Guide to the Guerrilla TV Archive 1965-1997 MSS 138 MSS.138
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series VII: Audio Recordings, 55163
  - Subseries A: Guerrilla TV Interviews, 55211
    - Nick DeMartino, Washington DC, 12/14/1981; 138.0037; 55333 (Box 12, Cassette 138.0037, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0037)
      Original Format: 1/4" Audiocassette, TDK AD-C60, Duration: 58 min.
      Preservation note: "Side 1: 00:00:00;xx-00:00:20;xx - Loud statis/intereference; Interview over the phone with occasional electrical interference"
    - Nick DeMartino, discusses Washington Community Video, Public Interest Video Network, Carnegie Commission, the public trust and keeping pace with new TV. 1 of 2, 5/23/1984; 138.0038; 55332 (Box 12, Cassette 138.0038, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0038)
      Original Format: 1/4" Audiocassette, Sony CHF90, Duration: 95 min.
    - Nick DeMartino, discusses Washington Community Video, Public Interest Video Network, Carnegie Commission, the public trust and keeping pace with new TV. 2 of 2, 5/23/1984; 138.0039; 55331 (Box 12, Cassette 138.0039, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0039)
      Original Format: 1/4" Audiocassette, Sony CHF90, Duration: 28 min.
    - Janet Densmore, New Orleans "Algiers Incident"., 2/3/1984; 138.0040; 55330 (Box 12, Cassette 138.0040, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0040)
      Original Format: 1/4" Audiocassette, TDK AD90, Duration: 78 min.
    - Blaine Dunlop, Atlanta, discusses Broadside TV and collaboration with Sol Korine., 4/17/1983; 138.0041; 55329 (Box 12, Cassette 138.0041, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0041)
      Original Format: 1/4" Audiocassette, TDK SA90, Duration: 94 min.
    - Bonnie Engel, San Francisco, Founder of Mobius Video Festival, 10/8/1983; 138.0042; 55328 (Box 12, Cassette 138.0042, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0042)
      Original Format: 1/4" Audiocassette, TDK AD90, Duration: 83 min.
    - Mary Esbjornson, New York, discusses UCV and Intermedia Arts., undated; 138.0043; 55327 (Box 12, Cassette 138.0043, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0043)
      Original Format: 1/4" Audiocassette, JVC GI-90, Duration: 77 min.
      Preservation note: "Side 1: 00:00:30;xx - 00:02:05;xx - O-speed issue from source, corrected; Side 2: Fluctuating speed issue throughout, very difficult to understand content - attempt was made to make corrections with very limited success"
    - Kit Fitzgerald and John Sanborn. Part 1 of 2, 12/19/1981; 138.0044; 55326 (Box 12, Cassette 138.0044, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0044)
    - Kit Fitzgerald and John Sanborn. Part 2 of 2, 12/19/1981; 138.0045; 55325 (Box 12, Cassette 138.0045, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0045)
    - Davidson Gigliotti. Part 1 of 2, 12/9/1981; 138.0046; 55324 (Box 12, Cassette 138.0046, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0046)
      Original Format: 1/4" Audiocassette, TDK AD-C60, Duration: 67 min.
    - Side one: Davidson Gigliotti, Side two: Kitty Morgan. Part 2 of 2, 12/9/1981; 138.0047; 55323 (Box 12, Cassette 138.0047, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0047)
      Original Format: 1/4" Audiocassette, TDK AD-C60, Duration: 57 min.
    - Sharon Goldenberg, Encino CA, discusses feminist video in Vermont, now in cable, 10/13/1983; 138.0048; 55322 (Box 12, Cassette 138.0048, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0048)
      Original Format: 1/4" Audiocassette, TDK AD90, Duration: 65 min.
    - Paul Goldsmith, Los Angeles, disccusses TVTV genres, 10/13/1983; 138.0049; 55321 (Box 12, Cassette 138.0049, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0049)
    - Shalom Gorewitz, 12/15/1981; 138.0050; 55320 (Box 12, Cassette 138.0050, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0050)
      Original Format: 1/4" Audiocassette, TDK AD-C60, Duration: 62 min.
    - Marie Gould, NOVAC, 2/1/1984; 138.0051; 55319 (Box 12, Cassette 138.0051, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 38.0051)
      Original Format: 1/4" Audiocassette, Laser UHDIC90, Duration: 43 min.
      Preservation note: "Side 1: 00:12:30;xx - 00:22:27;xx - O-significant electronic static inherent in the source it escalates until it becomes very difficult to hear the content, and then abruptly stops; Side 2 is blank"
    - John Giancola, New York, NYSCA, 6/11/1984; 138.0052; 55318 (Box 12, Cassette 138.0052, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0052)
      Original Format: 1/4" Audiocassette, Sony LNX90, Duration: 54 min.
    - Julie Gustafson, New York, discusses Global Village Documentaries. Part 1 of 2, 4/13/1984; 138.0053; 55317 (Box 12, Cassette 138.0053, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0053)
      Original Format: 1/4" Audiocassette, Maxell UD90, Duration: 90 min.
    - Julie Gustafson, New York, discusses Global Village Documentaries. Part 2 of 2, 4/13/1984; 138.0054; 55316 (Box 12, Cassette 138.0054, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0054)
      Original Format: 1/4" Audiocassette, Maxell UD90, Duration: 38 min.
    - DeeDee Halleck, 6/14//1986; 138.0055; 55315 (Box 12, Cassette 138.0055, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0055)
      Original Format: 1/4" Audiocassette, Sony LNX90, Duration: 82 min.
    - Barbara Haspiel, discusses NYSCA and video funding, 5/7/1984; 138.0056; 55314 (Box 12, Cassette 138.0056, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0056)
      Original Format: 1/4" Audiocassette, Sony LNX90, Duration: 94 min.
    - Mike Hazard, Minneapolis, University Community Video, 6/17/1983; 138.0057; 55313 (Box 12, Cassette 138.0057, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0057)
      Original Format: 1/4" Audiocassette, Scotch BX90, Duration: 73 min.
      Preservation note: "Some transport "squeak" noticeable towards the end of both sides"
    - John Hellmore, Los Angeles, "Odd discussion, peripherally about Vermont Video Group and UCV", 10/13/1983; 138.0058; 55312 (Box 12, Cassette 138.0058, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0058)
      Original Format: 1/4" Audiocassette, TDK AD90, Duration: 60 min.
    - Dorothy Hnault discussing George Stoney and Challenge for Change, 6/2000; 138.0059; 55311 (Box 13, Cassette 138.0059, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0059)
      Original Format: 1/4" Audiocassette, TDK D90, Duration: 48 min.
      Preservation note: "Content in left channel only (re-mixed into both channels); Side 2 is blank; Sporadic static/electrical intereference throughout [from source]"
      Conditions Governing Access
      This title is currently unavailable.
    - Jamie Hindman and Larry Kirkman discussing AFI, 12/4/1981; 138.0060; 55310 (Box 12, Cassette 138.0060, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0060)
      Original Format: 1/4" Audiocassette, TDK Ad-C60, Duration: 50 min.
      Preservation note: "Sporadic static/electrical intereference throughout [from source]"
    - Perrin Ireland, Washington DC, discussing NEA support for video documentaries, 5/22/1984; 138.0061; 55309 (Box 13, Cassette 138.0061, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0061)
      Original Format: 1/4" Audiocassette, Sony LNX90, Duration: 46 min.
    - Jane Jensen, New Orleans, discusses NOVAC, 2/3/1984; 138.0062; 55308 (Box 13, Cassette 138.0062, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0062)
      Original Format: 1/4" Audiocassette, Laser UHDIC90, Duration: 00
      Preservation note: "Entire tape is blank no capture"
    - Deanna Kamiel, Minneapolis, discusses Independent production staff at KCTA and women in television, 6/14/1983; 138.0063; 55307 (Box 13, Cassette 138.0063, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0063)
      Original Format: 1/4" Audiocassette, TDK SA90, Duration: 89 min.
    - Judi Keleman, Boston, Women's Video Collective, 11/10/1983; 138.0064; 55306 (Box 13, Cassette 138.0064, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0064)
      Original Format: 1/4" Audiocassette, TDK AD90, Duration: 46 min.
    - Joanne Kelly, San Francisco, discusses Video Free America and the problems of being a woman in video and documentary. Part 1 of 2, 10/7/1983; 138.0065; 55305 (Box 13, Cassette 138.0065, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0065)
      Original Format: 1/4" Audiocassette, TDK AD90, Duration: 93 min.
      Preservation note: "Side 2: 00:33:10;xx - 00:45:30;xx [end] - background hum like a vacuum cleaner being run; Overall fidelity on both side is low."
    - Joanne Kelly, San Francisco, discusses Video Free America and the problems of being a woman in video and documentary. Part 2 of 2, 10/7/1983; 138.0066; 55304 (Box 13, Cassette 138.0066, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0066)
      Original Format: 1/4" Audiocassette, TDK AD90, Duration: 43 min.
      Preservation note: "Low fidelity; Side 2 is blank"
    - Howard Klein, New York, discusses Rockefeller Foundation and video funding., 3/20/1984; 138.0067; 55303 (Box 13, Cassette 138.0067, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0067)
      Original Format: 1/4" Audiocassette, TDK AD-C90, Duration: 95 min.
      Preservation note: "Side 2: @ 00:10:40;xx content changes, this remaining content has sporadic electronic interference recorded into source tape"
    - Carole Anne Klonarides and Robin White, Soho TV. Part 2 of 2, 11/18/1981; 138.0068; 55301 (Box 13, Cassette 138.0068, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0068)
      Original Format: 1/4" Audiocassette, Lafayette Criterion 60, Duration: 95 min.
    - Luci Kostelanetz, discusses NYSCA, 5/2/1984; 138.0069; 55300 (Box 13, Cassette 138.0069, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0069)
    - Mitchell Kriegman, Part 1 of 2, 12/3/1981; 138.0070; 55299 (Box 13, Cassette 138.0070, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0070)
      Original Format: 1/4" Audiocassette, TDK Ad-C60, Duration: 63 min.
    - Mitchell Kriegman, Part 2 of 2, 12/3/1981; 138.0071; 55298 (Box 13, Cassette 138.0071, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0071)
      Original Format: 1/4" Audiocassette, TDK AD-C60, Duration: 42 min.
    - Stephen Kulczycki, Los Angeles, discusses UCV and its collapse as a production house, 10/14/1983; 138.0072; 55297 (Box 13, Cassette 138.0072, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0072)
      Original Format: 1/4" Audiocassette, TDK AD90, Duration: 85 min.
    - Ben Levine, discusses People's Video Theater and Woodstock Community Video. Part 1 of 2, 11/1/1984; 138.0073; 55296 (Box 13, Cassette 138.0073, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0073)
      Original Format: 1/4" Audiocassette, Scotch BX90, Duration: 89 min.
    - Ben Levine, discusses People's Video Theater and Woodstock Community Video. Part 2 of 2, 11/1/1984; 138.0074; 55295 (Box 13, Cassette 138.0074, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0074)
    - Wendy Lidell, AIVF, 12/3/1981; 138.0075; 55294 (Box 13, Cassette 138.0075, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0075)
    - Chip Lord, San Francisco, Ant Farm, 10/3/1985; 138.0076; 55293 (Box 13, Cassette 138.0076, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0076)
      Original Format: 1/4" Audiocassette, TDK AD90, Duration: 69 min.
    - David Loxton, New York, discusses TV lab and TVTV among others, 4/2/1984; 138.0077; 55292 (Box 13, Cassette 138.0077, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0077)
      Original Format: 1/4" Audiocassette, Maxell UD90, Duration: 79 min.
    - Mary Lucier, 12/7/1981; 138.0078; 55291 (Box 13, Cassette 138.0078, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0078)
    - Mary Lucier, Part 1 of 2, 10/21/2001; 138.0079; 55290 (Box 13, Cassette 138.0079, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0079)
      Preservation note: "Content is in the left channel only; re-mixed to both channels for the access copy."
    - Mary Lucier, Part 2 of 2, 10/21/2001; 138.0080; 55289 (Box 13, Cassette 138.0080, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0080)
      Original Format: 1/4" Audiocassette, TDK D90, Duration: 28 min.
      Preservation note: "Content in left channel only; re-mixed to both channels for access copy. Side 2 is blank"
    - Curt Madison, 11/19/1984; 138.0081; 55288 (Box 13, Cassette 138.0081, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0081)
      Original Format: 1/4" Audiocassette, Scotch BX60, Duration: 32 min.
    - Victor Masayevsa, Jr., discusses Native American Festival, 11/16/1984; 138.0082; 55287 (Box 13, Cassette 138.0082, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0082)
      Original Format: 1/4" Audiocassette, Sanyo C-60, Duration: 63 min.
      Preservation note: "Side 2: Answering machine tape?"
    - Ron McCoy, discusses the origins of University Community Video, 6/9/1983; 138.0083; 55286 (Box 13, Cassette 138.0083, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0083)
      Original Format: 1/4" Audiocassette, TDK SA90, Duration: 87 min.
    - Susan Milano. Part 1 of 2, 6/15/1984; 138.0084; 55285 (Box 13, Cassette 138.0084, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0084)
      Original Format: 1/4" Audiocassette, Sony LNX990, Duration: 94 min.
      Preservation note: "Side 1: 7 minute gap at beginning removed."
    - Susan Milano. Part 2 of 2, 5/15/1984; 138.0085; 55284 (Box 13, Cassette 138.0085, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0085)
      Original Format: 1/4" Audiocassette, Sony LNX90, Duration: 14 min.
    - Mary Milton and the Markle Foundation, October 12, 19zz, undated; 138.0086; 55283 (Box 13, Cassette 138.0086, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0086)
      Original Format: 1/4" Audiocassette, Certron LN60, Duration: 18 min.
    - Jim Morris, San Francisco, discusses producing "The Stag Hotel", 10/5/1983; 138.0087; 55282 (Box 13, Cassette 138.0087, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0087)
      Original Format: 1/4" Audiocassette, TDK AD90, Duration: 79 min.
    - Jim Mulligan and Greg Pratt, Minneapolis, discuss UCV, its growth, development and the ongoing careers of both men, 6/14/1983; 138.0088; 55281 (Box 13, Cassette 138.0088, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0088)
      Original Format: 1/4" Audiocassette, TDK SA90, Duration: 86 min.
    - Marty Newell, Whitesburg KY, discusses "Headwaters" a weekly video cable show, Part 1 of 2, 1/24/1984; 138.0089; 55280 (Box 13, Cassette 138.0089, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0089)
    - Marty Newell, Whitesburg KY, discusses "Headwaters" a weekly video cable show, Part 2 of 2, 1/24/1984; 138.0090; 55279 (Box 13, Cassette 138.0090, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0090)
      Original Format: 1/4" Audiocassette, TDK AD90, Duration: 22 min.
    - Stevenson Palfi, Part 1 of 2, 8/9/1984; 138.0091; 55278 (Box 13, Cassette 138.0091, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0091)
    - Stevenson Palfi, Part 2 of 2, 8/9/1984; 138.0092; 55277 (Box 13, Cassette 138.0092, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0092)
      Original Format: 1/4" Audiocassette, Sony LNX90, Duration: 36 min.
    - Kath Quinn, New Orleans discusses NOVAC, the early years, 2/2/1984; 138.0093; 55276 (Box 13, Cassette 138.0093, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0093)
      Original Format: 1/4" Audiocassette, Laser UHDIC90, Duration: 47 min.
    - Karen Ranucci, New York, discusses DCTV, 6/13/1984; 138.0094; 55275 (Box 13, Cassette 138.0094, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0094)
      Original Format: 1/4" Audiocassette, Sony LNX90, Duration: 93 min.
    - John Reilly, New York, Global Village, Part 1 of 2, 4/17/1984; 138.0095; 55274 (Box 13, Cassette 138.0095, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0095)
      Original Format: 1/4" Audiocassette, Maxell UD90
    - John Reilly, New York, Global Village, Part 2 of 2, 4/17/1984; 138.0096; 55273 (Box 13, Cassette 138.0096, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0096)
    - Sherrie Rabinowitz, Santa Monica CA, discusses Optic Nerve and Rabinowitz-Galloway Satellite collaboration Part 1 of 2, 10/18/1983; 138.0097; 55272 (Box 13, Cassette 138.0097, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0097)
      Original Format: 1/4" Audiocassette, TDK AD90, Duration: 87 min.
      Preservation note: "Tape folded in and reversed - repaired before proceeding with transfer; Side 1 becomes increasingly static-y and less audible as it goes along until by the end it is completely inaudible; Side 2 has poor audio quality but is completely audible throughout"
    - Sherrie Rabinowitz, Santa Monica CA, discusses Optic Nerve and Rabinowitz-Galloway satellite collaboration, Part 2 of 2, 10/19/1983; 138.0098; 55271 (Box 13, Cassette 138.0098, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0098)
      Original Format: 1/4" Audiocassette, TDK AD90, Duration: 35 min.
    - Alan Rucker, TVTV. Part 1 of 2, 10/18/1983; 138.0099; 55270 (Box 13, Cassette 138.0099, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0099)
    - Alan Rucker, TVTV. Part 2 of 2, 10/18/1983; 138.0100; 55269 (Box 13, Cassette 138.0100, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0100)
    - Alan Rucker, discusses TVTV's 20 year reunion. Part 1 of 2, 3/8/1992; 138.0101; 55268 (Box 13, Cassette 138.0101, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0101)
      Original Format: 1/4" Audiocassette, TDK D90, Duration: 77 min.
    - Alan Rucker, discusses TVTV's 20 year reunion. Part 2 of 2, 3/8/1992; 138.0102; 55267 (Box 13, Cassette 138.0102, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0102)
      Original Format: 1/4" Audiocassette, Maxell UR90, Duration: 19 min.
    - Paul Ryan, 10/29/1985; 138.0103; 55266 (Box 13, Cassette 138.0103, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0103)
      Original Format: 1/4" Audiocassette, TDK SA90
    - Michael Shamberg, Los Angeles, discusses TVTV. Part 1 of 2, 10/19/1983; 138.0104; 55265 (Box 13, Cassette 138.0104, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0104)
      Original Format: 1/4" Audiocassette, TDK AD90, 94 min.
    - Michael Shamberg, Los Angeles, discusses TVTV. Part 2 of 2, 10/19/1983; 138.0105; 55264 (Box 13, Cassette 138.0105, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0105)
      Original Format: 1/4" Audiocassette, TDK AD90, 16 min.
    - Ira Schneider and Deena Krane. Part 1 of 2, 12/17/1981; 138.0106; 55263 (Box 13, Cassette 138.0106, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0106)
      Original Format: 1/4" Audiocassette, Sony LNX90, 63 min.
    - Ira Schneider and Deena Krane. Part 2 of 2, 12/17/1981; 138.0107; 55262 (Box 13, Cassette 138.0107, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0107)
      Original Format: 1/4" Audiocassette, TDK AD-C60, 20 min.
    - Ira Schneider, 6/26/1984; 138.0108; 55261 (Box 13, Cassette 138.0108, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0108)
    - Kathy Seltzer, discusses Portable Channel, UCV and "The Fear the Binds Us", 6/16/1983; 138.0109; 55260 (Box 13, Cassette 138.0109, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0109)
      Original Format: 1/4" Audiocassette, TDK SA90, 47 min.
    - John Shepherd and Barbara London, AFI, 6/1982; 138.0110; 55259 (Box 13, Cassette 138.0110, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0110)
      Original Format: 1/4" Audiocassette, TDK AD-C60, 55 min.
    - Neil Sieling, Minneapolis, discusses UCV in transition, 6/17/1983; 138.0111; 55258 (Box 13, Cassette 138.0111, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0111)
      Original Format: 1/4" Audiocassette, Scotch BX90, 39 min.
    - Lydia Sillman, New York, discusses NYSCA and video, programming for 77-78, 5/1/1984; 138.0112; 55257 (Box 13, Cassette 138.0112, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0112)
      Original Format: 1/4" Audiocassette, TDK D90, 73 min.
    - Fred Simon, Boston, discusses pioneering video "Bobby the Fife," "New Wave," and "Frank: A Vietnam Vet", 11/9/1983; 138.0113; 55256 (Box 13, Cassette 138.0113, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0113)
      Original Format: 1/4" Audiocassette, TDK AD90, 95 min.
    - Thea Sklover, New York, discusses Open Channel Public Access, 8/25/1983; 138.0114; 55255 (Box 13, Cassette 138.0114, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0114)
      Original Format: 1/4" Audiocassette, TDK AD-C90, 81 min.
      Preservation note: "Side 2: @ 00:29:50.xx different content (a discussion about nuclear war rather than "guerilla tv")"
    - Ray Smith, Whitesburg KY, discusses the decline of Broadside TV, 1/25/1984; 138.0115; 55254 (Box 13, Cassette 138.0115, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0115)
      Original Format: 1/4" Audiocassette, TDK AD90, 90 min.
      Preservation note: "Side 2: - sporadic static bursts (sounds like a loose connection with the microphone wire)"
    - Karen Snyder and Karen Kern, New Orleans, discuss NOVAC and "From the Stoop", 2/4/1984; 138.0116; 55253 (Box 13, Cassette 138.0116, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0116)
      Original Format: 1/4" Audiocassette, TDK AD-C90, 69 min.
    - Elon Soltes, Los Angeles, discusses TVTV, the rift in the group toward the end, "Lord of the Universe" and April Video Collective. Part 1 of 2, 10/12/1983; 138.0117; 55252 (Box 13, Cassette 138.0117, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0117)
    - Elon Soltes, Los Angeles, discusses TVTV, the rift in the group toward the end, "Lord of the Universe" and April Video Collective. Part 2 of 2, 10/12/1983; 138.0118; 55251 (Box 13, Cassette 138.0118, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0118)
      Original Format: 1/4" Audiocassette, TDK AD90, 44 min.
    - Phillip Stack, Sony executive. Part 1 of 2, 10/3/1984; 138.0119; 55250 (Box 14, Cassette 138.0119, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0119)
      Original Format: 1/4" Audiocassette, OMNI Ultra Dynamic 90, 90 min.
    - Phillip Stack, Sony executive. Part 2 of 2, 10/3/1984; 138.0120; 55249 (Box 14, Cassette 138.0120, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0120)
      Original Format: 1/4" Audiocassette, OMNI Ultra Dynamic 90, 8 min.
      Preservation note: "Severe hydrolysis impedes tape transport on side 2 however side 2 appears to be blank; the 8 minutes of content on Side 1 was captured with no problem"
    - Adam Steg, New Orleans, discusses Synapse, NOVAC etc., 2/1/1984; 138.0121; 55248 (Box 14, Cassette 138.0121, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0121)
      Original Format: 1/4" Audiocassette, Laser UHDIC90, 47 min.
    - Bill Stephens, discussing the People's Communication Network. Part 1 of 2, 5/10/1984; 138.0122; 55247 (Box 14, Cassette 138.0122, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0122)
      Original Format: 1/8" Audiocassette, Sony LNX90
    - Bill Stephens, discusses the People's Communication Network. Part 2 of 2, 5/10/1984; 138.0123; 55246 (Box 14, Cassette 138.0123, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0123)
      Original Format: 1/4" Audiocassette, Sony LNX90
    - George Stoney Part 1 of 2, 6/15/1984; 138.0124; 55245 (Box 14, Cassette 138.0124, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0124)
      Original Format: 1/4" Audiocassette, Sony LNX90, 92 min.
      Preservation note: "Side 1: content trails of near the end in both volume and speed problems; Side 2 is fine"
    - George Stoney Part 2 of 2, 6/15/1984; 138.0125; 55244 (Box 14, Cassette 138.0125, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0125)
      Original Format: 1/4" Audiocassette, Sony LNX90, 37 min.
      Preservation note: "Side 1: content trails of near the end in both volume and speed problems; Side 2 is blank"
    - George Stoney Part 1 of 2, 6/27/2000; 138.0126; 55243 (Box 14, Cassette 138.0126, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0126)
      Original Format: 1/4" Audiocassette, Maxell UR90, 94 min.
      Preservation note: "Content in left channel only; re-mixed to both channels"
    - George Stoney Part 2 of 2, 6/27/2000; 138.0127; 55242 (Box 14, Cassette 138.0127, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0127)
      Original Format: 1/4" Audiocassette, Maxell UR90, 18 min.
      Preservation note: "Content is in left channel only; re-mixed to both channels; Side 2 is blank"
    - Skip Sweeney, San Francisco, Video Free America, 9/29/1983; 138.0128; 55241 (Box 14, Cassette 138.0128, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0128)
    - Skip Sweeney, San Francisco, Video Free America. Part 1 of 3, 10/2/1983; 138.0129; 55240 (Box 14, Cassette 138.0129, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0129)
      Original Format: 1/4" Audiocassette, Maxell XLII90, 1 min.
      Preservation note: "Side 1: 1 minute's worth of content; Side 2 is blank"